- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Kazuki Takahashi
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Gaius Maximus
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Kenji Yamamoto
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Hiroshi Nakamura
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Isamu Fujimoto
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Ryota Tanaka
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Toshiro Sato
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Marcus Valerius
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Akihiko Yoshida
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Decimus Brutus
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Haruki Watanabe
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Titus Aemilius
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta traveling samurai\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Yasuo Suzuki
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Lucius Tiberius
- question: "\n\t\tPick a name for a character based on the following description: \n\t\t\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t\ta roman legionary\n\t\t\"\"\"\n\t"
  answer: Sextus Aurelius
